Krisztian Nemeth



Web Developer and Designer

Personal Statement

I am a web developer with 3+ years of experience in designing and developing web-based products from planning to deployment. I use skills that I gained during my studies at City of Glasgow College, as well as skills developed during studies on my own time.

I am in pursuit of a career where I could leverage my technical skills and creativity to produce accessible, responsive, functional, and visually pleasing websites and applications.

Work Experience

Freelance Web Developer

2022 - Current

- Design: Planning and prototyping
- Development: Building websites and applications from scratch with various technologies based on a brief or my own designs
- Problem solving: Identifying and resolving interface, functionality or performance related issues
- Usability/Accessibility testing: Ensuring that a product is suitable for target audiences, and is accessible and responsive on a wide range of devices
- Hosting and deployment

Shift Leader at Caffe Nero

2017 - Current

- Team Management: Leading a team, ensuring the delivery of quality customer service
- Customer Service: Actively engaging with customers, taking and completing orders, handling complaints
- Operational Duties: Handling responsibilities opening and closing the store, cashing up, ordering and managing stock
- Quality Control: Ensuring that food and beverages are prepared and served according to standards maintaining consistency and quality
- Problem Solving: Identifying and solving issues that may arise, such as staffing shortages or equipment malfunctions, ensuring the smooth operation of the store
- Training: Assisting in the training and development of new team members, providing guidance and support

Education

HND - Web Development (Grade A) 2022-2023 / City of Glasgow College

HNC - Digital Design and Web Development (Grade A)

2021-2022 / City of Glasgow College

Contact Info

Phone: +44 7545 026642

E-mail: hello@krisnemeth.dev Portfolio: krisnemeth.dev

Skills

Technologies

JavaScript / HTML / CSS / SASS / TailwindCSS / Bootstrap / PHP / MySQL / React / Redux / Git

Languages

English - fluent, living in the UK since 2017

Hungarian - native

Other skills

Always looking to improve and learn new skills

Efficient learner, able to adapt to new environments

Good communication and people skills (exbartender/barista)

Organized, great team worker, able to work independently

Management and leadership experience, also great follower